privilege and not a career and the politicians are supposed to answer to
the American people and not the opposite, when will your administration be putting
together a proposal for term limits for Congress? Well we're looking into that
right now. Right now I want to get those congressmen to go and approve it about Obamacare and all the. Well, we're looking into that right now.
Right now, I want to get those congressmen to go and approve Obamacare and all the different
things that we're working on.
One step at a time.
We'll be doing it, really.
I mean, that's something down the road a little bit.
A lot of people don't like that.
Frankly, you know, they consider term limits to be an election, but I think it would be
a good thing.
But right now, what I want to do is get Obamacare approved and I want people to love us.
Approved or changed?
Well, really, well, changed when I say Obamacare.
I mean, I'm talking about real change.
And I suspect the first thing that's going to change will be the name.
But we're talking about repealing and replacing.
And if we don't do that, I would be very upset.
Nobody's going to get thrown out of their insurance, are they?
Because that's what a lot of people are saying on the left.
They're saying millions of people are gonna lose the insurance.
No, they have it all wrong.
And you're gonna hear about it during the speech, but they have it all wrong.
We're gonna have a really great healthcare plan, and
it's gonna be much more affordable, including for the country.
Go ahead.
I know when you were inaugurated, you put your hand on your Bible that your mother
had given you as a child.
I know as a mother, as parents, we pray for our children.
We want the best for them.
And your parents, they probably prayed for you so much, but maybe not, they might not
have realized that you were going to get this far.
And I know they would be very proud of you.
That leads me to this question.
Ronald wrote us and said,
I pray for you daily.
Do you take time to pray?
I do actually.
And to me it's very important, but that's so nice.
Who is that?
That's Ronald.
Well, hello Ronald.
We ought to bring Ronald to the White House.
He'd be happy to come.
I like Ronald.
And this is the last one.
Alan Sherman from Queen says,
I'm a diehard New York Mets fan since you're a native of the Great Borrower Queens, but moved to Manhattan.
Are you a Mets fan or a Yankees fan? The fate of the world relies on this answer.
Well, I don't think it does, but actually, I do like both teams.
And I love the Steinbrenner family and the Wilpont family and Randy Levine and the whole group.
Randy has done a terrific job. He's involved with the Yankees.
Now you're probably going to win New York.
Well, I don't know, but I do like both teams.
I really do.
What about Social Security?
People my age are worried that it might run out by the time we need it.
You're going to be okay.
That was Angelie from Manhattan.